A Guide to the Papers of the YWCA of Hampton Roads 1910s-1990s
Special Collections, Perry Library, Old Dominion University
- Photos
  - Sports and Fitness
    - Red Cross Swimming Class, July 1964 (Box Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Swimming-Virginia Beach, YWCA (Box Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Gym Photos, 1979 (Box Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Tennis Photos, 1995 (Box Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Tennis Auction Photos, October 3, 1997 (Box Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Lady Monarchs Photos (I), 1997 (Box Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Lady Monarchs Photos (II), 1997 (Box Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Gym Photos (Box Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Fitness (Box Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Golf Photos (Box Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Events
    - The Thursday Club, 1961 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Ladies Day Out, 1961 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Coronation Ball, 1963 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Beach Ladies Day Out and Evening Coed Class, 1963 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Kempsville Ladies Day Out, November 1963 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Leisure Hour Affair (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Leisure Hour, May 1963 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Adult Talent-Fashion Show at Freemason Branch, 1967 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Black and White Fashion Show Photos, 1970s (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Beauty Pageant (I) (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Beauty Pageant (II) (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Black and White Photos-First Step, 1987 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Lynnhaven Mall, 1988 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Leisure Hour Club Luncheon, 1994 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Mask Making-First Night, 1995 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Festevents, September 1996 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Town Point Park-Festival (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Busch Gardens Photos (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 18)
    - 96X Photos (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Dollar Drinks/The Coast (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Navy Chief Selectees (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 21)
    - YWCA Open House (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 22)
    - YWCA Celebrate a New Beginning, Holiday Inn Waterside (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 23)
    - YWCA Celebrate a New Beginning (Black and White) (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 24)
    - YWCA Salute to Volunteers (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Event at Chesapeake Hotel (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Day of Caring, September 9, 1993 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Day of Caring, September 8, 1994 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Day of Caring-Work Party (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Day of Caring-Miscellaneous (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Phyllis Wheatley Event (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Backyard Picnic, 1970s (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Picnics (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Political
    - Civil Rights Photos (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Voter Registration Project, July 1964 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Vigil/Meeting Photos (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Chuck Robb Photos, 1982 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Drum Out/Speak Out, 1993 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Meetings
    - Meeting Photos (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Award/Meeting Photos (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Membership Meeting-Speaker: Margaret Adain, October 1967 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 8)
    - STOP-Annual Meeting, November 1980 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 9)
    - YWCA Meeting Photos, 1986 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Grand Affairs Meeting, 1988 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Annual Meeting/Reception, July 1997 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Color Meeting Photos, 1980s-1990s (I) (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Color Meeting Photos, 1980s-1990s (II) (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 14)
    - House Meeting Photos, 1990s (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Myera Obendorf Meeting Photos (Opening at Little Neck Road Center) (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Training, Team Building, Retreats, and Conferences
    - Virginia State Conference, March 1965 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Volunteer Leadership, October 8, 1966 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Sing Out Richmond-Midwinter Conference, 1967 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 19)
    - World Fellowship (Lake Wright), 1969 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 20)
    - World Fellowship Luncheon (Sheraton Inn), 1970 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Language Arts Workshop, November 13, 1980 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Board Retreat, November 15, 1980 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 23)
    - WIC Training Photos, 1984 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 24)
    - YWCA Leadership Photos (I), 1996 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 25)
    - YWCA Leadership Photos (II), 1996 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 26)
    - "What a Team" Slides (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Staff Member Training with NSC Students (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Obstacle Course Photos (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 3)
    - YWCA Triennial Convention (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Household Training Institute Class (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Panel (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Workshop Photos-Miscellaneous (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Other Titled Photos
    - Black and White Group Photo, 1960s (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 8)
    - NYC Enrollees, 1970 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Diocese of Southern Virginia Photos, 1970s (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 10)
    - House Gathering Photos, 1980s-1990s (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Women in Crisis Photos (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Church Women United, November 1980 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Photocopies of YWCA Headquarters Photo (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 14)
    - World Photos (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Backyard Photos, 1993 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Bug Photo (date unknown) (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Church (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 18)
    - YWCA Snack Bar (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous/Dated Slides, Photos, Negatives
    - Miscellaneous Photos, 1960s (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous Black and White Photos, 1960s (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Black and White Photos, 1965 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous Photos, 1970s (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous Color Photos, 1970s-1980s (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Black and White Photos, 1980s (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous Photos, 1980s (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Photos, 1984 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Black and White Photos, 1980s-1990s (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Photos, 1980s-1990s (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Photos, 1993 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Photos, 1994 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Miscellaneous/Undated Slides, Photos, Negatives
    - Tables and Displays-Miscellaneous (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Black and White Photos (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Photos (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Slides-Reference (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Slides-MB Main Building (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Slides-SH Shelter (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Slides-MC Mother Center (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Slides-H History (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Slides-Y Programs (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Slides-O Events (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Slides-B Board Meetings (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Slides-Faye Lee (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Slides (I) (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Slides (II) (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Photo Negatives (I) (color) (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Photo Negatives (II) (disc) (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Photo Negatives (III) (black and white) (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Color Negatives (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Negatives (I) (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Negatives (II) (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Negatives (III) (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Negatives (IV) (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Undeveloped Slides (in box) (Box Box 13)
    - Rolls of Film (3) (in box) (Box Box 13)
    - Rolls of Film (2) (in box) (Box Box 13)
    - Rolls of Film (4) (in box) (Box Box 13)
- Artifacts
  - YWCA Balloon, Name Tags, Sign Letters, Silk Flower, Ruler, Envelope, Scenic Postcard (Box Box 14)
  - "Legislative Wrap Up Announcement" (Box Box 15)
  - YWCA Committee on Administration, 1962 (Box Box 15)
  - Exercise Photos (Box Box 15)
  - Ballet/Dance Photo (Box Box 15)
  - Old Man Photo (Box Box 15)
  - Ballet/Dance Photo (Box Box 15)
  - Articles, 1940s (2) (Box Box 15)
  - Articles, 1930s (3) (Box Box 15)
  - Articles, 1950s (1) (Box Box 15)
  - Selling of Camp Owaissa (Box Box 15)
  - Women's Articles (1970s) (Box Box 15)
  - Photos of Jacox Junior High and Old Dey Lodge (Box Box 15)
  - Women's Articles (1970s-Includes Faith Prior Rollins Obituary) (Box Box 15)
  - Beacon Article, 1988 (Box Box 15)
  - 1940s Picture and Articles (ODU Archives Photo) (Box Box 15)
  - Photos-First Women in Norfolk Fire and Police Department (Box Box 15)
  - Dr. Carmelita Williams and Mrs. Shirley S. Whitehead (Box Box 16)
  - First Baptist Church Home for the Aged (Box Box 16)
  - Original Homes for the Aged (Box Box 16)
  - Secretary Photo (1940s) (Box Box 16)
  - Phyllis Wheatley Snack Bar (Box Box 16)
  - Wilkshaw Residence (Box Box 16)
  - Group Photos (1950s or 1960s) (Box Box 16)
  - Department of Public Health Permit for YWCA Cafeteria, 1968 (Box Box 16)
  - YWCA Park Avenue Group Photo (Copy from the Journal and Guide), 1955 (Box Box 16)
  - Cookout Photo (Box Box 16)
  - Cookout Photo (Box Box 16)
  - Scrapbook, 1921 (Box Box 17)
  - Scrapbook, 1923 (Box Box 17)
  - Phyllis Wheatley Album, 1960s-1970s (Box Box 18)
  - Scrapbook Phyllis Wheatley Branch B. and P. Club (Box Box 18)
  - Clippings, 1962-1964 (Box Box 18)
  - Scrapbook, 1924-1928 (Box Box 19)
  - Scrapbook, 1923-1932 (Box Box 19)
  - Scrapbook, 1952-1954 (Box Box 20)
  - Scrapbook, 1951 (Box Box 21)
  - Scrapbook, 1925 (Box Box 22)
  - Thursday Club Scrapbook, 1925-1954 (Box Box 22)
  - Ladies Day Out Scrapbook, 1946-1958 (Box Box 23)
  - Scrapbook, 1954-1955 (Box Box 23)
  - Scrapbook, 1963 (Box Box 24)
  - Scrapbook-TRIS/Sexual Assault Articles, 1970s (Box Box 24)
  - Scrapbook-Tidewater Rape Information Services (TRIS), 1980s (Box Box 24)
  - Guest Book Women's History Exhibit 1982 (Box Box 24)
  - Response Scrapbook, 1990s (Box Box 24)
  - Scrapbook-Education Clippings (Box Box 24)
  - Slides, 1950s-1990s (Box Box 25)
  - Scrapbook, 1961-1970 (Box Box 25)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1970s (oversize) (Box Box 26)
  - Scrapbook, 1962-1964 (Box Box 26)
  - Scrapbook, 1968-1971 (Box Box 26)
  - Scrapbook, 1971-1973 (Box Box 26)
  - Scrapbook, 1973-1974 (Box Box 26)
  - Scrapbook, 1932-1934 (Box Box 27)
  - Phyllis Wheatley Scrapbook, 1942-1945 (Box Box 27)
  - Scrapbook, 1950 (Box Box 27)
  - Mostly blank scrapbook, with 1970s photos in middle (Box Box 27)
  - Scrapbook, 1959-1961 (Box Box 28)
  - Scrapbook, 1981-1985 (Box Box 28)
  - Scrapbook, 1970-1972 (Box Box 29)
  - Scrapbook, 1962-1972 (Box Box 29)
  - Scrapbook, 1936-1938 (Box Box 30)
  - Scrapbook, 1920s (Box Box 30)
  - Scrapbook, 1959-1966 (Box Box 31)
  - Photo-Tidewater Community College instructors of "Dealing with Sexual Assault" (Box Box 32)
  - Princess Anne Virginia Beach Certification (Box Box 32)
  - Photo of a Navy Ship (Box Box 32)
  - "Why Volunteer?" (Box Box 32)
  - Bookmark (Box Box 32)
  - Women in Transition Phone Number (Box Box 32)
  - Clare's Win Dir documents-WP 5.1 (Box Box 33)
  - Y-Prep Radio Spot (Box Box 33)
  - Lucille Ball-YW Today-Radio (Box Box 33)
  - PSA United Way "Thank You" February, 1990 (Box Box 34)
  - NSU-"Live and in Color," Norfolk State University, Office of Admissions (Box Box 34)
  - Toward a Drug Free America, United Way of South Hampton Roads (Box Box 34)
  - "Your Vote Counts," WAVY TV 10 and the League of Women Voters of Norfolk/Virginia Beach (Box Box 34)
  - YWCA Women in Crisis (Box Box 35)
  - YWCA Women in Transition (Box Box 35)
  - Women as Winners (Box Box 36)
  - Women as Winners (Box Box 36)
  - Public Service Announcements on the Homeless and Child Care (Box Box 36)
  - Public Service Announcements on Women as Winners, the Homeless and Child Care (Box Box 36)
  - Department of Social Services, PSA 1988 (Box Box 37)
  - R.F.A.R.R. ODU Basketball/Season Tickets November 23, 1987 (Box Box 37)
  - Virginians Against Domestic Violence 1988 (Box Box 37)
  - Greenbrier Chrysler-Plymouth 1988 (Box Box 37)
  - Box of Audiocassettes (Box Box 38)
  - TRIS (Tidewater Rape Information Services) Banner (Box Box 39)